"lang"
{
"Language"	"schinese"
"Tokens"
{
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_1"	"在一片广阔的战场上，两个对立的军团战火连绵。\n他们分别叫做天辉和夜魇，各由5名玩家组成。\n摧毁对方遗迹的军团将宣告游戏的胜利。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_1"	"In Dota, two teams face each other across a vast battlefield.\nThe teams, called Radiant and Dire, are each made up of 5 players.\nWhichever team is able to destroy the opposing team's Ancient will claim victory."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_2"	"在这片战场上分布着很多重要地点。\n有怪兽丛生的野区，也有划分双方阵营的河道。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_2"	"Across the battlefield are scattered a number of important locations.\nFrom monster infested jungles to the river, which divides the team's starting territories."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_3"	"比赛开始后，每个玩家都将从眼花缭乱的英雄中选个一名，\n并使用自己的初始金钱购买一堆廉价装备。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_3"	"As the match begins, each player chooses a Hero from a diverse roster,\nand then spends their starting gold on a handful of inexpensive items."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_4"	"双方基地中都有三组兵营，小兵将从这里出发，他们不受玩家控制。\n沿着上中下三条路向敌方基地行进。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_4"	"Within each Base are three sets of Barracks, where uncontrollable units called Creeps march forth.\nThese Creeps progress down one of the three lanes toward the enemy Base."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_5"	"每条分路各由三座防御塔进行守卫，防御塔将攻击行进的小兵和英雄。\n在游戏前期，英雄的实力普遍不强，需要与小兵同行，由他们进行掩护。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_5"	"Each lane is protected by three defensive Towers, which will attack advancing Creeps or Heroes.\nIn the early stages of battle, Heroes have yet to gather their strength, and may wish\nto travel with their Creeps for protection from enemy Creeps and other forces."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_6"	"随着战斗的进行，英雄可以通过击杀小兵和敌方英雄获得金钱和经验。\n借此来加强实力，对敌方阵营的外部防御塔发起攻势。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_6"	"As the battle continues, Heroes kill enemy Creeps and enemy Heroes to gain gold and experience.\nThis will allow them to gain power and begin assaulting the enemy Team's outer defensive Towers."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_8"	"河道有神符产生，神符能够为英雄带来各种临时性的加成。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_8"	"The river is the source of Runes. Runes provide temporary, but powerful bonuses."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_9"	"有时候英雄在野区攻击中立生物更为安全，\n适当时机下，他们会前往肉山的巢穴，\n为了得到他身上具有复活效果的不朽之守护将其合力击杀。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_9"	"Heroes might sometimes find it safer to attack Neutral Creeps in the jungles,\nor they may gather to assault the mighty Roshan in his lair, hoping to harvest\nhis resurrecting Aegis of Immortality."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_10"	"最后，一方的力量足够强大，就能突入敌方基地，\n摧毁敌方兵营，这样那条路上的小兵将会升级。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_10"	"In time, a Team will become powerful enough to advance their forces into the enemy Base,\nwhere they may destroy the enemy Barracks to grant themselves Mega-Creeps in that lane."
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_11"	"只要他们突破了敌方的内部防线，\n接下来对遗迹发起进攻并将其摧毁即可宣告胜利。"
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_11"	"Once they have breached the enemy's inner defenses,\nthe Team must attack and destroy the Ancient to claim victory."
}
}
