"lang"
{
"Language"	"brazilian"
"Tokens"
{
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_2"	"No campo de batalha estão distribuídos vários locais importantes.\nDe florestas infestadas por monstros até o rio, que divide os territórios de cada equipe."
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_2"	"Across the battlefield are scattered a number of important locations.\nFrom monster infested jungles to the river, which divides the team's starting territories."
}
}
