"lang"
{
"Language"	"swedish"
"Tokens"
{
"Tutorial.NPXDEM_1"	"I Dota möter två lag varandra på ett stort slagfält.\nLagen, som heter Radiant och Dire består av 5 spelare vardera.\nDet lag som förstör det andra lagets Ancient kommer segra."
"[english]Tutorial.NPXDEM_1"	"In Dota, two teams face each other across a vast battlefield.\nThe teams, called Radiant and Dire, are each made up of 5 players.\nWhichever team is able to destroy the opposing team's Ancient will claim victory."
}
}
